const defaultGameData = {
  boards: [
    {
      categories: [
        "FIRST",
        "DELULU",
        "FAVOURITE",
        "SHREYA THINGS",
        "MILESTONE"
      ],
      questions: [
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question: "Who was my first crush?",
            answer: "Shawn Fernandes ",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 400,
            question: "What was my first car?",
            answer: "Kia Picanto",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 600,
            question: "When was the first time I came to Australia for Uni?",
            answer: "Feb 2019",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 800,
            question: "Who was my first pet?",
            answer: "Billu",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 1000,
            question: "What was my first pair of mainstream shoes?",
            answer: "Air Force Ones",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
{
            points: 200,
            question: "Also known as telepathy",
            answer: "What is mind reading?",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 400,
            question: "I wanted to become this before I pursued Chemical Enginenering?",
            answer: "Doctor",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 600,
            question: "I want this artist to come to my wedding",
            answer: "Who is Lauv?",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 800,
            question: "I want a house in this suburb",
            answer: "What is Vaucluse?",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 1000,
            question: "A thumbs up signifies being upset",
            answer: "What is Shreya's communication skills?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
{
            points: 200,
            question: "What is my favourite colour?",
            answer: "Yellow",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 400,
            question: "What is my favourite fruit?",
            answer: "Mango",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 600,
            question: "What is my favourite Chinese street food?",
            answer: "Malatang",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 800,
            question: "What is my favourite sport?",
            answer: "Basketball",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 1000,
            question: "What is my favourite spot in Sydney?",
            answer: "Sydney Park",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
{
            points: 200,
            question: "Sometimes I put these on my head and ask where did I keep them",
            answer: "Glasses",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 400,
            question: "A biological cycle every month",
            answer: "Hot water bag",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 600,
            question: "Morning drink",
            answer: "Jeera Water",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 800,
            question: "How do I greet my mom when she calls me?",
            answer: "Amma, heli",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 1000,
            question: "My father wants to hit me with this",
            answer: "Chapli (slipper)",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
{
            points: 200,
            question: "When did I graduate from UNSW?",
            answer: "2021",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 400,
            question: "When is my citizenship exam?",
            answer: "28th Aug",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 600,
            question: "When did I get my PR",
            answer: "December 2023",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 800,
            question: "At whatr age I learn how to drive?",
            answer: "22",
            revealed: false,
          },
{
            points: 1000,
            question: "Where did I win my first badminton tournament?",
            answer: "China",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ]
      ],
    },
  ],
  defaultPlayers: [
    { name: "Player 1", score: 0 },
    { name: "Player 2", score: 0 },
  ],
};

// Export the game data
export { defaultGameData };
